=== Subiz Live Chat ===
Contributors: mrsubiz
Donate link: 
Tags: live chat agent customer service tips, subiz, subiz live chat, online sale, website sale, widget, plugin, sidebar, enhancement, livechat, chat, chat online, contact plugin, contact us, customer support, customer service, free chat, chat software, chat plugin, sale plugin, onine sale plugin, IM chat, live chat, live chat inc, live chat services, live chat software, live chatting, live help, live support, live web chat, livehelp, livesupport, olark, online chat, online support, online support plugin, php live chat, snapengage, support software, website chat, wordpress chat, wordpress live chat, wordpress live chat plugin, Zopim, zendesk, Zopim live chat, banckle, clickdesk, click desk, helpdesk, 
Requires at least: 2.8
Tested up to: 4.2.2
Stable tag: 1.1
License: GPLv2 or later
License URI: http://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-2.0.html

An on-site live chat plugin to turn your passive website into a real store by personalization and human touch!

== Description ==

Using hotline or email as the main communication channel with customers may bring many drawbacks for online businesses as their visitors can be left to passively surf the store or wait for the unresponsive email system or the busy hotline service. Subiz live chat is designed as a web-based plugin to solve these entire problems.

[Subiz Live Chat](http://subiz.com/?utm_source=plugin_wp&utm_medium=link&utm_campaign=plugin_wp1.1) offers excellent communication platform where website owner can engage directly with visitors, fulfill every single enquiry in real-time, and actively receive feedback. All of these interaction would happen on a chat widget docked at the pre-determined place on the webpage, running in real-time while visitor are exploring the website. This fully functional live chat tool will turn website visitor into paying customers, increase conversion rates, and generate more loyal customers.

[youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vuoZw77XivQ]

Subiz is a free chat plugin which is specifically designed for your WordPress site. This plugin will boost your sales and customer satisfaction.

**Plugin Features:**

* Dashboard offers unique method to target visitors: who they are, where they come from, what they are looking for
* From Dashboard display, sales and customer service team can actively approach visitors with a chatting invitation and provide direct support. Subiz allows up to 200 concurrent coversations
* Chat widget can be fully customized to match with website display: size, color, theme, avatar, font,...
* Customer service team can support for visitors on the go from any device using 3rd-party apps such as Pidgin, Adium, Trillian
* Trigger, an automatic feature, enables supporter to send chat invitations automatically based various preset rules
* Subiz assure safety of data by storing chat history in a secure server
* Subiz enables agent to be assigned to groups by which business owner can manage effectively sales and support performance 
* Google Analytics are integrated to provides operational reporting

Language available: English, Português, Français, Italiano, Español, Deutsch, Tiếng Việt, 中文, فارسی

Subiz combines all powerful features into a live chat solution to provide premium customer service. 
A website without subiz is nothing different comparing to a store without salesperson. 

Apply Subiz Live Chat plugin now and [sign up here](https://dashboard.subiz.com/signup.html?utm_source=plugin_wp&utm_medium=link&utm_campaign=plugin_wp1.1) for free!

**Don't forget to follow and love Subiz:**
[Support Center](http://support.subiz.com/support/home/?utm_source=plugin_wp&utm_medium=link&utm_campaign=plugin_wp1.1),
[Blog](http://subiz.com/blog/?utm_source=plugin_wp&utm_medium=link&utm_campaign=plugin_wp1.1),
[Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/subizdotcom),
[Twitter](https://twitter.com/subizdotcom),

== Installation ==

* Install Subiz plugin from WordPress directory and activate it.
* Under Settings section, click on Subiz Live Chat which links to your Subiz account
* Enter your Subiz email account and password.
* Customize chat widget to match your preference.
* Visit your website, you should see your Subiz chat box at the bottom of your site.
* Finally, from Dashboard, manage your visitors and start chat.

== Frequently asked questions ==

= Do I have to install any software on my server to get this working? =
Not at all! Subiz is a hosted live chat service. Simply configure the plugin and you're done!

= Which web browsers work best with this plugin? =
Though designed to work on most browsers, Subiz works best in the following environment: IE 6 or later, Firefox 2 or later, Safari 2 or later, Google Chrome.

= Is it free to use? =
The plugin comes with a free plan specially tailored for WordPress users. Power users can purchase upgrade options anytime.

= How can I upgrade my account? =
Follow the instruction to create Subscription: [How to create subscription](http://support.subiz.com/support/solutions/articles/3000004814-how-to-create-a-subscription-?utm_source=plugin_wp&utm_medium=link&utm_campaign=plugin_wp1.1)

= How can I invite visitors to chat? =
There are 2 ways:

* Manually: You can click to each visitor displayed on list to chat with them 
* Automatically: If you are in premium user, you can use Trigger as a tool to invite visitors to chat proactively.

= How can I customize live chat widget? =
Go to Dashboard >> Settings >> Chat widget >> Theme

* **Color:** On the right hand-side, you can choose the 5 given colors or customize which color you like.
* **Widget position:** You can choose the widget's position on the left or right.
* **Logo:** In the third part on the right, click to upload logo image (image size must not exceed 50Kb)
* **Language:** You can switch language on chat widget into a certain language (English, Português, Français,...) or choose Auto Detect mode

= How can I know when my visitors send messages? =
There 3 types of notification for you to alert when you have incoming messages from visitors

* Sound
* Notify number
* Desktop Notification

= Is there any further support to help me utilise Subiz effectively? =
You may face with many difficulties installing and using Subiz. Don't worry! You can find a ton of useful tips regarding live chat & customer service on [Subiz Blog](http://subiz.com/blog/?utm_source=plugin_wp&utm_medium=link&utm_campaign=plugin_wp1.1). Otherwise, just chat with our support heroes at [subiz.com](http://subiz.com/?utm_source=plugin_wp&utm_medium=link&utm_campaign=plugin_wp1.1) or leave us an email at support@subiz.com.


== Screenshots ==
1. Chat widget on website
2. Manage visitors on Dashboard
3. Customize widget from Dashboard

== Changelog ==

= 1.1 =
* New language available for live chat widget


= 1.0 = 

* Update documentation for new version
* Update banner and screenshot image

== Upgrade notice ==



== Arbitrary section 1 ==

